A Guide to the Institute of International Education records, Alumni and Historical Files, RG 1 FA1289
Rockefeller Archive Center
Institute of International Education records, Alumni and Historical Files, RG 1
1924-1997
Rockefeller Archive Center
Institute of International Education (New York, N.Y.)
FA1289
1108 Reels 1108 reels of microfilm including 550 reels of unique content and duplicates.
1110 reels of microfilm including 550 reels of unique content and duplicates.
Arrangement
Arranged in three series as follows: Series 1: Alumni Files, 1924-1970; Series 2: Grantee Files, 1967-1997; Series 3: Historical Files. Each series is loosely arranged chronologically, and further arranged alphabetically by grantee. Records remain in order as received.
Biographical / Historical
The Institute of International Education (IIE) was established in 1919 by Nobel Prize winners Nicholas Murray Butler, Elihu Root and Stephen Duggan, Sr. The founders sought greater understanding among nations, primarily through the establishment of international educational exchange between United States institutes of higher education and foreign actors interested in formulating and developing active and ongoing educational understanding. As the Institute grew, developed and matured, it has continued to focus in the area of scholars exchange, as well as education services, international development and leadership training.
IIE initially focused on facilitating student, faculty, and teacher exchanges with European countries. In the 1930s their scope expanded beyond Europe to include exchanges between the Soviet Union and Latin America. During this period the Institute also established the Emergency Committee to Aid Displaced German Scholars which later expanded to include scholars fleeing facist Spain and Italy as well. In the 1950s this program was utilized to support Hungarian refugees. In the early 2000s IIE Trustees together with other donors endowed the Scholar Rescue Fund (SRF).
Following WWII, the Institute helped establish the Association of International Educators (NAFSA) and the Council on International Education Exchange (CIEE) for which they serve to administer the CIEE faculty component and the graduate student component of the Fullbright program, which continues to today as the Institute's largest program.
Scope and Contents
The Alumni Files and the Grantee Files comprise an estimated 3 million files which pertain to the students and professors involved in the IIE's exchange programs, and document the administration of their awards and travel.
The Historical Files pertain to the administration of the IIE's programs.
It is recommended that the Alumni Files and Grantee Files be used in concert with the Grantee Locator cards available in IIE, Record Group 2 (FA1290). The Grantor Locator cards are an alphabetical index of the Alumni/Grantees. The cards primarily provide program and date information as well as field of study. The cards can also be used as an entry point to the microfilm, with many of the cards providing roll number, side number and index number for the given grantee.
The microfilm of the Alumni Files and Historical files was created 1965-1970. As such the film shows physical wear, and at times can be extremely difficult to read. The overwhelming majority of the microfilm reels are double-sided, with content on both sides. To view the second side, fast forward to the end of the reel, proceed backwards and adjust the image and view settings accordingly.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The microfilm was transferred to RAC by the Institute of International Education through several accessioned in 2017. The original Alumni Files and Historical Files were destroyed at the time of microfilming (1965-1970) and are therefore not a part of the archival collection.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Other Finding Aids
Institute of International Education records are available in the following other finding aids:
Institute of International Education records, Fellowship Cards (Grantee Locator Cards), RG 2 (FA1290)
Institute of International Education records, Publications, Paper records, RG 3, Series 1 (FA1291)
Institute of International Education records, Publications, Microforms, RG 3, Series 2 (FA1315)
Institute of International Education records, Photographic Files, RG 4 (FA1288)
Related Materials
The Council for International Exchange of Scholars (CIES) collection is available at the University of Arkansas.
The Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced Foreign Scholars records are available at the New York Public Library.
The International Fellowship Fund (IFF) Archives are available at Columbia University.
- Alumni Files, 1924-1970; 1
  Scope and Contents
  The Alumni Files and the Grantee Files comprise an estimated 3 million files which pertain to the students and professors involved in the IIE's exchange programs, and document the administration of their awards and travel. For the Alumni Files, the date provided represents the date that the given microfilm reel was created. The creation dates of the contents of the reel are provided within the title field.
  Arrangement
  Loosely arranged chronologically, and further arranged alphabetically by grantee. Records remain in order as received.
  - 1925-1926 - 1932-1933 - 253 American Students, 1925-1933 (Reel 1)
  - 1932-1933 - 1934-1935 - 253 American Students, 1965 July 30 (Reel 2)
  - 1934-1935 - 1935-1936 - 253 American Students; 1924-1925 - 1931-1932 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 August 2 (Reel 3)
  - 1931-1932 - 1933-1934 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 August 5 (Reel 4)
  - 1933-1934 - 1935-1936 - 252 Foreign Students (Reel 5)
  - 1931-1932 - 1932-1933 - 252 Foreign Students; 1934-1935 - 1935-1936 - 253 American Students, 1965 August 13 (Reel 6)
  - 1934-1935 - 1935-1936 - 252 Foreign Students; 1934-1935 - 253 American Students, 1965 August 17 (Reel 7)
  - 1935-1936 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 August 19 (Reel 8)
  - 1935-1936 - 220; 1935-1936 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 August (Reel 9)
  - 1935-1936 - 253 American Students, 1965 August 25 (Reel 10)
  - 1935-1936 - 1936-1937 - 220; 1936-1937 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 August 30 (Reel 11)
  - 1936-1937 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 September 1 (Reel 12)
  - 1936-1937 - 253 American Students, 1965 September 3 (Reel 13)
  - 1937-1938 - 220; 1937-1938 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 September 8 (Reel 14)
  - 1937-1938 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 September 12 (Reel 15)
  - 1937-1938 - 1938-1939 - 252 Foreign Students; 1937-1938 - 1938-1939 - 253 American Students, 1965 September 14 (Reel 16)
  - 1937-1938 - 1938-1939 - 220; 1938-1939 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 September 21 (Reel 17)
  - 1938-1939 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 September 24 (Reel 18)
  - 1938-1939 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 September 28 (Reel 19)
  - 1938-1939 - 253 American Students, 1965 October 13 (Reel 20)
  - 1938-1939 - 220 and 252 Foreign Students; 1939-1940 - 253 American Students (Reel 21)
  - 1939-1940 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 October 19 (Reel 22)
  - 1940-1941 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 October 20 (Reel 23)
  - 1939-1940 - 1940-1941 - 252 Foreign Students; 1939-1940 - 1940-1941 - 253 American Students, 1965 October 22 (Reel 24)
  - 1941-1942 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 October 22 (Reel 25)
  - 1941-1942 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 October 27 (Reel 26)
  - 1941-1942 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 October 28 (Reel 27)
  - 1941-1942 - 252 Foreign Students; 1941-1942 - 253 American Students, 1965 November 1 (Reel 28)
  - 252 Foreign Students and 253 American Students, 1965 November 3 (Reel 29)
  - 1944-1945 - 1945-1946 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 November 12 (Reel 30)
  - 1944-1945 - 1945-1946 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 November 8 (Reel 31)
  - 1947-1948 - 1948-1949 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 November 24 (Reel 32)
  - 1947-1948 - 1948-1949 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 November 30 (Reel 33)
  - 1947-1948 - 1948-1949 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 December 6 (Reel 34)
  - 1949-1950 - 252 Foreign Students; 1949-1950 - 253 American Students, 1965 December 16 (Reel 35)
  - 1950-1951 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 December 15 (Reel 36)
  - 1950-1951 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 December 30 (Reel 37)
  - 1949-1950 - 252 Foreign Students; 1949-1950 - 253 American Students, 1965 December 27 (Reel 38)
  - 1951-1952 - 252 Foreign Students; 1951-1952 - 253 American Students, 1966 January 4 (Reel 39)
  - 1951-1952 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 January 12 (Reel 40)
  - 1951-1952 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 January 17 (Reel 41)
  - 1951-1952 - 252 Foreign Students; 1951-1952 - 253 American Students, 1966 January 19 (Reel 42)
  - 1951-1952 - 252 Foreign Students; 1951-1952 - 253 American Students, 1966 January 20 (Reel 43)
  - 1951-1952 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 January 24 (Reel 44)
  - 1951-1952 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 January 27 (Reel 45)
  - 1952-1953 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 January 31 (Reel 46)
  - 1952-1953, 1966 February (Reel 47)
  - 1952-1953 - 252 Foreign Students; 1952-1953 - 253 American Students, 1966 February 17 (Reel 48)
  - 1951-1952 - 252 Foreign Students; 1927 - 220, 1966 April 8 (Reel 49)
  - 1942, 1927, 1929-1930 - 220, 1966 February 9 (Reel 50)
  - 1932, 1934, 1941 - 220, 1966 February 14 (Reel 51)
  - 1929-1930, 1938-1941 - 220, 1966 February 16 (Reel 52)
  - 1924-1926, 1947-1948, 1949-1950 - 220, 1966 February 21 (Reel 53)
  - 1929-1933 - 220, 1966 February 24 (Reel 54)
  - 1952-1953 - 220, 1966 February 28 (Reel 55)
  - 1953-1954 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 March 3 (Reel 56)
  - 1952-1953 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 March 7 (Reel 57)
  - 1952-1953, 1953-1954 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 March 10 (Reel 58)
  - 1952-1953, 1953-1954 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 March 14 (Reel 59)
  - 1953-1954 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 March 17 (Reel 60)
  - 1953-1954 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 March 22 (Reel 61)
  - 1952-1953, 1953-1954 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 March 24 (Reel 62)
  - 1953-1954 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 March 29 (Reel 63)
  - 1930-1931, 1953-1954, 1954-1955 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 April 1 (Reel 64)
  - 1953-1954, 1954-1955 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 April 5 (Reel 65)
  - 1953-1954, 1954-1955 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 April 12 (Reel 66)
  - 1954-1955 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 April 15 (Reel 67)
  - 1953-1954 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 April 3 (Reel 68)
  - 1954-1955 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 May 9 (Reel 69)
  - 1954-1955 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 May 12 (Reel 70)
  - 1954-1955 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 May 17 (Reel 71)
  - 1954-1955 - 253 American Students; 1955 - 276 Summer School, 1966 May 23 (Reel 72)
  - 1954-1955 - 252 Foreign Students; 1954-1955 - 276 Summer School, 1966 May 26 (Reel 73)
  - 1954-1955 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 March 6 (Reel 74)
  - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 February 14 (Reel 75)
  - 1952-1953, 1953-1954 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 February 21 (Reel 76)
  - 1952-1953, 1953-1954 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 February 21 (Reel 77)
  - 1952-1953, 1953-1954 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 February 25 (Reel 78)
  - 1952-1953, 1953-1954 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 March 2 (Reel 79)
  - 1952-1953, 1953-1954 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 March 4 (Reel 80)
  - 1953-1954 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 March 8 (Reel 81)
  - 1953-1954 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 March 10 (Reel 82)
  - 1953-1954 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 March 12 (Reel 83)
  - 1953-1954 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 March 12 (Reel 84)
  - 1953-1954 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 March 23 (Reel 85)
  - 1953-1954 - 253 American Students, 1966 March 29 (Reel 86)
  - 1953-1954 - 253 American Students, 1966 April 2 (Reel 87)
  - 1954-1955 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 April 6 (Reel 88)
  - 1954-1955 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 April 12 (Reel 89)
  - 1954-1955 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 April 15 (Reel 90)
  - 1954-1955 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 April 20 (Reel 91)
  - 1954-1955 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 April 25 (Reel 92)
  - 1954-1955 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 April 28 (Reel 93)
  - 1954-1955 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 May 4 (Reel 94)
  - 1954-1955 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 May 9 (Reel 95)
  - 1954-1955 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 May 13 (Reel 96)
  - 1954-1955 - 253 American Students, 1966 May 19 (Reel 97)
  - 1955-1956 - 252 Foreign Students; 1955 - 276 Summer School, 1966 May (Reel 98)
  - 1954-1955, 1955-1956 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 June 2 (Reel 99)
  - 1955-1956 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 June 21 (Reel 100)
  - 1955-1956 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 June 15 (Reel 101)
  - 1955-1956 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 July 20 (Reel 102)
  - 1955-1956 - 253 American Students, 1966 June 23 (Reel 103)
  - 1955-1956 - 253 American Students and 252 Foreign Students, 1966 June 29 (Reel 104)
  - 1955-1956 - 253 American Students, 1966 July 6 (Reel 105)
  - 1955-1956, 1956-1957 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 July 12 (Reel 106)
  - 1956-1957 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 July 15 (Reel 107)
  - 1956-1957 - 252 Foreign Students; 1956-1957 - 253 American Students, 1966 August 4 (Reel 108)
  - 1956-1957 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 August 10 (Reel 109)
  - 1956-1957 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 August 15 (Reel 110)
  - 1956-1957 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 August 19 (Reel 111)
  - 1956-1957 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 August 31 (Reel 112)
  - 1956-1957 - 253 American Students; 1957 - 276 Summer School, 1966 September 6 (Reel 113)
  - 1956-1957 - 253 American Students, 1966 September 12 (Reel 114)
  - 1957 - 276 Summer School; 1954-1955 - 253 American Students, 1966 September 30 (Reel 115)
  - 1957-1958 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 September 22 (Reel 116)
  - 1957-1958 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 September 23 (Reel 117)
  - 1956-1957, 1957-1958 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 October 6 (Reel 118)
  - 1956-1957, 1957-1958 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 September 11 (Reel 119)
  - 1956-1957, 1957-1958 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 October 18 (Reel 120)
  - 1956-1957, 1957-1958 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 September 26 (Reel 121)
  - 1956-1957, 1957-1958 - 253 American Students, 1966 September 2 (Reel 122)
  - 1957-1958 - 253 American Students, 1966 November 14 (Reel 123)
  - 1956-1957, 1957-1958, 1958-1959 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 November 22 (Reel 124)
  - 1955-1956 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 June 10 (Reel 125)
  - 1955-1956 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 June 16 (Reel 126)
  - 1955-1956 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 June 20 (Reel 127)
  - 1955-1956 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 June 22 (Reel 128)
  - 1955-1956 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 June 29 (Reel 129)
  - 1954-1955, 1955-1956 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 July 21 (Reel 130)
  - 1956-1957 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 June 25 (Reel 131)
  - 1955-1956 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 August 1 (Reel 132)
  - 1956-1957 - 252 Foreign Students; 1956-1957 - 253 American Students, 1966 August 15 (Reel 133)
  - 1956-1957 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 August 24 (Reel 134)
  - 1956-1957 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 August 29 (Reel 135)
  - 1956-1957 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 August 31 (Reel 136)
  - 1956-1957 - 253 American Students, 1966 September 8 (Reel 137)
  - 1955-1956, 1956-1957, 1957-1958 - 252 Foreign Students and 253 American Students, 1966 September 14 (Reel 138)
  - 1955-1956, 1957-1958 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 September 20 (Reel 139)
  - 1956-1957, 1957-1958 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 September 26 (Reel 140)
  - 1956-1957, 1957-1958 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 September 28 (Reel 141)
  - 1956-1957 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 October 4 (Reel 142)
  - 1957-1958 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 October 10 (Reel 143)
  - 1957-1958 - 252 Foreign Students and 253 American Students, 1966 October 15 (Reel 144)
  - 1957-1958 - 252 Foreign Students and 253 American Students, 1966 October 18 (Reel 145)
  - 1957-1958 - 252 Foreign Students and 253 American Students, 1966 October 31 (Reel 146)
  - 1957-1958 - 252 Foreign Students and 253 American Students; 1958 - 276 Summer School, 1966 November 4 (Reel 147)
  - 1957-1958 - 252 Foreign Students and 253 American Students, 1966 November 14 (Reel 148)
  - 1958-1959 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 November 18 (Reel 149)
  - 1958-1959 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 November 29 (Reel 150)
  - 1958-1959 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 December 2 (Reel 151)
  - 1958-1959, 1959-1960 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 December 9 (Reel 152)
  - 1958-1959, 1959-1960 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 December 15 (Reel 153)
  - 1958-1959 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 December 22 (Reel 154)
  - 1958-1959 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 December 30 (Reel 155)
  - 1958-1959 - 252 Foreign Students; 1958 - 276 Summer School, 1967 January 13 (Reel 156)
  - 1958-1959 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 January 24 (Reel 157)
  - 1958-1959, 1959-1960 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 January 31 (Reel 158)
  - 1958-1959, 1959-1960 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 February 6 (Reel 159)
  - 1959-1960 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 February 20 (Reel 160)
  - 1959-1960 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 February 20 (Reel 161)
  - 1959-1960 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 March 6 (Reel 162)
  - 1959-1960 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 March 9 (Reel 163)
  - 1959-1960 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 March 29 (Reel 164)
  - 1959-1960 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 April 4 (Reel 165)
  - 1959-1960 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 April 10 (Reel 166)
  - 1959-1960 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 April 17 (Reel 167)
  - 1958-1959, 1959-1960 - 252 Foreign Students and 253 American Students, 1967 April 26 (Reel 168)
  - 1958-1959, 1959-1960 - 253 American Students, 1967 May 10 (Reel 169)
  - 1959-1960 - 253 American Students, 1967 May 24 (Reel 170)
  - 1959-1960-1961 - 252 Foreign Students; 1960 - 276 Summer School, 1967 June 12 (Reel 171)
  - 1960-1961 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 June 22 (Reel 172)
  - 1957-1958, 1958-1959, 1959-1960 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 June 29 (Reel 173)
  - 1960-1961 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 July 7 (Reel 174)
  - 1958-1959 - 252 Foreign Students; 1960 - 276 Summer School, 1966 November 29 (Reel 175)
  - 1958-1959, 1959-1960 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 November 9 (Reel 176)
  - 1958-1959 - 252 Foreign Students, 1966 December 16 (Reel 177)
  - 1958-1959 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 January 3 (Reel 178)
  - 1958-1959, 1959-1960 - 252 Foreign Students; 1958 - 276 Summer School, 1967 January 24 (Reel 179)
  - 1959-1960 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 January 30 (Reel 180)
  - 1957-1958, 1959-1960 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 February 9 (Reel 181)
  - 1959-1960 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 March 1 (Reel 182)
  - 1959-1960 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 March 17 (Reel 183)
  - 1958-1959, 1959-1960 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 April 4 (Reel 184)
  - 1959-1960 - 252 Foreign Students; 1959-1960 - 276 Summer School; 1958-1959, 1959-1960 - 253 American Students, 1967 April 21 (Reel 185)
  - 1958-1959 - 253 American Students, 1967 May 3 (Reel 186)
  - 1959-1960 - 253 American Students, 1967 May 23 (Reel 187)
  - 1959-1960 - 252 Foreign Students; 1959-1960 - 276 Summer School, 1967 June 14 (Reel 188)
  - 1960-1961 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 June 30 (Reel 189)
  - 1960-1961 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 July 7 (Reel 190)
  - 1964-1965 - 253 American Students, 1967 July 13 (Reel 191)
  - 1960-1961 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 July 19 (Reel 192)
  - 1960-1961 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 July 24 (Reel 193)
  - 1960-1961 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 July 28 (Reel 194)
  - 1960-1961 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 July 4 (Reel 195)
  - 1960-1961 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 August 4 (Reel 196)
  - 1960-1961 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 August 7 (Reel 197)
  - 1960-1961 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 August 9 (Reel 198)
  - 1960-1961 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 August 23 (Reel 199)
  - 1960-1961 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 August 23 (Reel 200)
  - 1960-1961 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 July 12 (Reel 201)
  - 1960-1961 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 August 21 (Reel 202)
  - 1960-1961 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 September 8 (Reel 203)
  - 1960-1961 - 253 American Students, 1967 September 15 (Reel 204)
  - 1960-1961 - 253 American Students, 1967 September 21 (Reel 205)
  - 1960-1961 - 253 American Students; 1960-1961 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 September 27 (Reel 206)
  - 1960-1961 - 253 American Students, 1967 October 2 (Reel 207)
  - 1960-1961 - 253 American Students, 1967 October 13 (Reel 208)
  - 1960-1961 - 253 American Students, 1967 December 13 (Reel 209)
  - 1960-1961 - 253 American Students, 1968 January 8 (Reel 210)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students; 1961 - 276 Summer School, 1968 February 1 (Reel 211)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 February 15 (Reel 212)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 February 21 (Reel 213)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 February 26 (Reel 214)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 March 6 (Reel 215)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 March 18 (Reel 216)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 March 19 (Reel 217)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 March 25 (Reel 218)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 April 8 (Reel 219)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 April 17 (Reel 220)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 April 24 (Reel 221)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 May 1 (Reel 222)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 May 6 (Reel 223)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 May 7 (Reel 224)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 October 11 (Reel 225)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1967 October 23 (Reel 226)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 October 22 (Reel 227)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 June 4 (Reel 228)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 July 3 (Reel 229)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 July 9 (Reel 230)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 July 10 (Reel 231)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 July 10 (Reel 232)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 July 19 (Reel 233)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 July 21 (Reel 234)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1965 August 9 (Reel 235)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 August 29 (Reel 236)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 September 4 (Reel 237)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 September 6 (Reel 238)
  - 1961-1962 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 September 10 (Reel 239)
  - 1961-1962 - 253 American Students, 1968 September 13 (Reel 240)
  - 1961-1962 - 253 American Students, 1968 September 26 (Reel 241)
  - 1961-1962 - 253 American Students, 1968 October 15 (Reel 242)
  - 1962-1963 - 252 Foreign Students; 1962-1963 - 276 Summer School, 1968 October 31 (Reel 243)
  - 1962-1963 - 252 Foreign Students, 1968 November 8 (Reel 244)
  - 1962-1963 - 252 Foreign Students, 1969 February 17 (Reel 245)
  - 1962-1963 - 252 Foreign Students, 1969 February 19 (Reel 246)
  - 1962-1963 - 252 Foreign Students, 1969 February 20 (Reel 247)
  - 1962-1963 - 252 Foreign Students, 1969 February 26 (Reel 248)
  - 1962-1963 - 252 Foreign Students - Eldemairy - Germinbessidou, 1969 April 7 (Reel 249)
  - 1962-1963 - 252 Foreign Students - Gerritsen - Grounes, 1969 April 8 (Reel 250)
  - 1962-1963 -252 Foreign Students - Gruber - Han, Sung-Joo, 1969 April 8 (Reel 251)
  - 1962-1963 - 252 Foreign Students - Han, Than Soe - Hirschman, Prof. Aberto, 1969 April 8 (Reel 252)
  - 1962-1963 - 252 Foreign Students - Hoerz, Mr. Dieter - Irahim, Mr. Abou-Bakrklalil, 1969 April 8 (Reel 253)
  - 1962-1963 - 252 Foreign Students - Ibrahim, Mr. George Elias - Jacquemain, Miss Michels Suzanne, 1969 April 9 (Reel 254)
  - 1962-1963 - 252 Foreign Students - Jacusiel, Kirschstein, Miss Vera - Kanno, Akira, 1969 April 9 (Reel 255)
  - 1962-1963 - 252 - Kapadia, Mr. Zarirj - Khansunguvorn, Mr. Boorson, 1969 April 9 (Reel 256)
  - 1962-1963 - 252 Foreign Students - Khatio, Mr. Omar Ismail - Kortay, Miss Goksel, 1969 April 10 (Reel 257)
  - 1962-1963 - Kove, Nicholas Akoto Gbeckon - Lamy, Francine Helen Fany 40, 1969 April 10 (Reel 258)